Guide to the the Richard W. Lyman, President of Stanford University, Papers SC0215
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Papers, Series 3
  - Directories: Faculty/Staff/Student, January 1976 - August 1977; AD3.8 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Form Letters, January 1971 - June 1978; AD3.9 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Fundamental Standard (Honor Code), December 1976 - October 1978; AD3.10 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Mailings, ID Mail, February 1974 - December 1978; AD3.13 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Stanford Seal/Motto, April 1961 - April 1976; AD3.16 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - University Calendar/Holidays, September 1976 - October 1978; AD3.21 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Speeches, RWL's and Others, January 1978 - March 1978; AD3.22 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - President's Office, June 1975 - November 1978; AD4 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - Presidential Powers, AD4.2 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - President's House, Staff, Car, March 1976 - May 1978; AD4.7 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - President's Schedule, May 1972 - December 1978; AD4.9 (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - Presidential Staff Meetings, June 1974 - December 1978; AD4.11 (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - Vice Presidential Group, October 1978; AD4.12 (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - Academic Secretary, December 1968 - November 1978; AD4.14 (Box 29, Folder 45)
  - University Counsel, August 1970 - June 1978; AD4.19 (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - Congratulation Letters, September 1978 - December 1978; AD4.20.3 (Box 29, Folder 47)
  - Invitation general, 2/78-12/78; AD4.20.4 (Box 29, Folder 47.1)
  - Invitations accepted, 9/78-12/78; AD4.20.4/1 (Box 29, Folder 47.2)
  - Complaints/Nonsense, September 1978 - September 1977; AD4.20.5 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Public Affairs Office, November 1977 - December 1978; AD4.22 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Southern California Office, April 1970 - April 1976; AD4.23 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - New York Office, September 1972 - December 1976; AD4.24 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Ombudsman, August 1977 - December 1978; AD6 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Legal Problems & Services, January 1973 - October 1978; AD7 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Dr. Nancy Jewell Cross, AD7 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Campus Disruptions and Demonstrations, November 1972 - April 1978; AD7.2 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Student Discipline: Inquiries/General Info, AD7.2.3 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Dean of Student Cases, June 1976 - October 1978; AD7.2.5 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - SJC (Stanford Judicial Council) (Cases), March 1976 - July 1978; AD7.2.7 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Founding Grant, January 1971 - July 1976; AD7.6 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - University Governance, October 1970 - March 1976; AD7.8 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Judicial Procedures/Charter, April 1975 - December 1976; AD7.9 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Policy: Participation in Politics, January 1976 - February 1976; AD7.13 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Admissions Office, January 1976 - October 1978; AD8.1 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Policy: Admissions/General, March 1977 - November 1978; AD8.1.1 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Bakke Case (Admissions Policy), January 1976 - December 1977; AD8.1.1/1 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Admissions Cases, May 1978 - April 1979; AD8.1.2 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Students on Committees, Policy, AD8.5 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Career Planning and Placement Center, November 1976 - September 1978; AD8.7 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - College Work-Study, October 1970 - February 1978; AD8.7.2 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Dean of Student Affairs, February 1976 - December 1978; AD8.8 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Invitation, General, February 1978 - December 1978; AD4.20.4 (Box 30, Folder 48)
  - Invitations Accepted (Keep 1 yr. & review), September 1978 - December 1978; AD4.20.4/1 (Box 30, Folder 49)
  - Student Services and Special Services Office, June 1970 - March 1976; AD8.8.2 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Policy on Discrimination, July 1976 - December 1978; AD8.8.3 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Student Counseling Services, October 1973 - May 1977; AD8.8.4 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - "The Bridge", March 1974 - April 1979; AD8.8.5 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Exchange Programs, April 1975 - December 1978; AD.8.10 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Intern Programs, December 1970 - October 1978; AD8.10.2 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Stanford Overseas Studies Programs, October 1976 - October 1978; AD8.11 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Stanford Center in Vienna, February 1970 - June 1977; AD8.11.1 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Stanford Center in Britain, January 1968 - May 1978; AD8.11.2 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Stanford Program in Tours, December 1970 - November 1976; AD8.11.3 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Stanford Program in Berlin, November 1976 - July 1977; AD8.11.4/1 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Stanford Program in Bonn, January 1977; AD8.11 4/2 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Stanford Center in Italy, July 1970 - March 1976; AD8.11.5 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Financial Aids, July 1976 - December 1978; AD8.12 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Student Loans, August 1966 - December 1978; AD8.12.1 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Graduate Student Financial Aid, December 1972 - July 1978; AD8.12.2 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Guide Service, March 1974 - June 1977; AD8.15 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Housing: Faculty, Staff, Emeriti, October 1976 - December 1978; AD8.18 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Housing Office, miscellaneous reports, 7/74-12/77; AD8.18.1 (Box 31, Folder 18.1)
  - Hanna-Honeycomb House, May 1972 - December 1978; AD8.18.2 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Lake House, September 1977 - October 1978; AD8.18.3 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Escondido Village, February 1975 - November 1978; AD8.18.7 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Fraternities/Sororities [2 folders], September 1977 - December 1977; AD8.18.8 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Housing for Students, September 1976 - May 1978; AD8.18.11 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Residence Halls / Staff, April 1973 December 1978; AD8.18.12 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Registrar, October 1976 - October 1978; AD8.21 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Enrollment Data, October 1976 - November 1978; AD8.21.1 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Minority Enrollment, January 1976 - October 1978; AD8.21.2 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Black Affairs, May 1977 - December 1978; AD9.1 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Chicano Affairs, September 1978 - November 1978; AD9.2 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Assistant to the President for Chicano Affairs, March 1976 - October 1978; AD9.2.1 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - MECHA, August 1968 - March 1977; AD9.2.2 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Native American Indian Affairs, March 1973 - March 1978; AD9.3 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Affirmative Action Office, August 1978 - December 1978; AD9.6 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Affirmative Action for Women, September 1976 - December 1977; AD9.6.3 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Personnel and Employee Relations, September 1976 - October 1978; AD10 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Employment Inquiries and Requests [2 folders], June 1972 - December 1979; AD10.1 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Policy: Appointment of Lecturers and Other Short-Term Teachers, September 1974 - August 1978; AD10.6 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Employee Organizations, December 1974; AD10.7 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Distaff Club, October 1975 - October 1977; AD10.7.1 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Committee for Art, December 1975 - August 1978; AD10.7.4 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Child Care, September 1975 - December 1977; AD10.7.5 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - United Stanford Employees, September 1976 - September 1978; AD10.7.8 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Personnel Policies / Hiring practices, April 1971 - September 1978; AD10.8 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Collective Bargaining, December 1975 - June 1977; AD10.8.2 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Policy: Benefits for Visiting Scholars, Fellows, AD10.8.9/2 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Grievance Procedures, Faculty/Staff, AD10.8.10 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Grievance Hearings: Cases, AD10.8.10/1 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Henry Organ Grievance, August 1977 - December 1979; AD10.8.10/1 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Grievances: Student/Faculty on Academic Matters, November 1975 - December 1976; AD10.8.10/3 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Short Term Disability, February 1978 - April 1979; AD10.8.14/4 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Long Term Disability, December 1977 - March 1978; AD10.8.14/5 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Leaves of Absences "Absences" etc, August 1975 - January 1979; AD10.8.15 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Early Retirement, January 1976 - October 1977; AD10.8.17/1 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Retirement Legislation, July 1977 - July 1979; AD10.8.17/2 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - TIAA CREF/Prudential, September 1978 - May 1979; AD10.8.17/3 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Salaries, January 1977 - August 1979; AD10.8.19 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Salaries: Other Institutions, May 1974; AD10.8.19/1 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - Policy: Travel, January 1976 - May 1979; AD10.8.21 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - Vacation, June 1978 - December 1978; AD10.8.23 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - Jury Duty, October 1970 - May 1977; AD10.8.26 (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - Archives, October 1970 - May 1977; AD11.1 (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - Food Service, June 1973 - September 1978; AD11.3 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Service Operations, January 1976 - March 1979; AD11.4 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Police Services/Campus Security, October 1978 - August 1979; AD11.6 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Office of Public Events, January 1976 - October 1978; AD11.7 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Founders' Day, February 1976 - March 1978; AD11.7.6 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Freshman Orientation, September 1978; AD11.7.7 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Publications Service/Communications, October 1972 - July 1978; AD11.8 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Copyright Policy, November 1977 - April 1978; AD11.8.1 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Records, Privacy of, December 1967 - October 1978; AD11.8.3 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Stanford News Service, January 1976 - October 1978; AD11.8.4 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - News Service Reports/Releases, October 1974 - October 1976; AD11.8.5 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Policy: Solicitation on Campus, July 1970 - March 1977; AD11.8.8 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Stanford Press, September 1978 - April 1979; AD11.8.9 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Stanford Publications, Misc, October 1978 - April 1979; AD11.8.11 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Stanford Facts, April 1977 - November 1978; AD11.8.11/1 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Television Instructional Network, January 1974 - June 1978; AD11.8.13 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Voluntary Organizations at Stanford, July 1970 - August 1979; AD11.9 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Business and Finance [2 folders], September 1978 - April 1979; AD12.2 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Business and Finance, Vice President for [missing], April 1976 - May 1979; AD12.2/1 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Auditing, April 1972 - January 1976; AD12.4 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Budgets, September 1978 - August 1979; AD12.5 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Room and Board Rates, February 1978 - November 1978; AD12.5.3 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Tuition, October 1978 - April 1979; AD12.5.4 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Wage and Price Freeze Issue, November 1978 - May 1979; AD12.5.5 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Policy: Investment Responsibilities, June 1978 - December 1978; AD12.7 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Consulting Policy/Conflict of Interest, May 1978 - December 1978; AD12.7.1 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Insurance/Risk Management, October 1976 - April 1978; AD12.8 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Health and Safety, June 1973 - December 1978; AD12.8.1 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Taxes; Tax Reform, February 1976 - January 1979; AD12.9 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Office of Development, September 1978 - April 1979; AD12.10.1 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Endowment: Stanford, September 1977 - May 1979; AD12.10.2 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Estates and Wills, February 1978 - May 1979; AD12.10.3/3 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Stanford Annual Fund (Inner Quad), October 1978 - February 1979; D12.10.3/4 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Gift Policies: Gift Summaries, September 1978 - June 1979; AD12.10.3/5 (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Gifts, (Permanent File) Misc, September 1978 - August 1979; AD12.10.3/5-1 (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - American Cancer Society, June 1970 - May 1979; AD12.10.3/5-2 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - American Heart Association, April 1972 - May 1978; AD12.10.3/5-3 (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - Annenberg, Walter H, April 1968 - May 1979; AD12.10.3/5-4 (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - Standard Oil of California, August 1972 - June 1978; AD12.10.3/5-5 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Bechtel Corporation, January 1966 - April 1979; AD12.10.3/5-7 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Bing, Peter S., M.D, May 1970 - May 1978; AD12.10.3/5-8 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Brown, Robert Minge and Gloria, February 1972 - September 1978; AD12.10.3/5-9 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Carnegie Foundation of New York, March 1975 - June 1979; AD12.10.3/5-10 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Childs, Jane Coffin Memorial Fund of Medical Research, November 1966 - June 1973; AD12.10.3/5-11 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Paul Cook, March 1975 - December 1975; AD12.10.3/5-11.5 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Criley, C.A, October 1971 - September 1979; AD12.10.3/5-12 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Crocker, Mrs. Roy P, October 1963 - January 1975; AD12.10.3/5-13 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Crown, John H. and Family, May 1972 - February 1976; AD12.10.3/5-14 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Cummings, Nathan, October 1972 - September 1976; AD12.10.3/5-15 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - de Basily, Mrs. Nicolas, December 1969 - June 1979; AD12.10.3/5-16 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Dickenson, Fairleigh S., Jr, March 1976 - June 1979; AD12.10.3/5-17 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Ducommun, Charles E. and Palmer G, December 1971 - June 1979; AD12.10.3/5-18 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - DuPont de Nemours Company, January 1966 - April 1978; AD12.10.3/5-19 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Ehrlich, Paul, May 1972 - February 1978; AD12.10.3/5-20 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Elliot Unitrust, July 1974 - July 1977; AD12.10.3/5-20.5 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Ely, Northcutt, January 1968 - February 1979; AD12.10.3/5-21 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - David L. Farnsworth Fund, May 1973 - February 1977; D12.10.3/5-22 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Farmers Insurance Group, September 1978 - October 1979; AD12.10.3/5-23 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - FNC Corporation, January 1978; AD12.10.3/5-23.5 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Ford Motor Company, December 1970 - December 1978; AD12.10.3/5-24 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Gates Foundation, January 1976 - February 1979; AD12.10.3/5-24.5 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - General Motors Corporation, Scholarship, Fellowships, General Gifts, August 1975 - November 1978; AD12.10.3/5-25 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Glenmede Trust Company, September 1976 - June 1979; AD12.10.3/5-26 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - R. Allen Griffin Fund, May 1975 - July 1978; AD12.10.3/5-26.5 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Guggenhime, Richard E, January 1973 - September 1978; AD12.10.3/5-27 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Hewlett Packard Company, February 1977 - September 1977; AD12.10.3/5-28 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Hewlett, William R. and Flora, April 1968 - July 1979; AD12.10.3/5-29 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Leukemia Society of America, Incorporated, November 1966 - April 1976; AD12.10.3/5-30 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Lewis, Roger, April 1972 - August 1979; AD12.10.3/5-31 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Maples, Roscoe, April 1966 - December 1978; AD12.10.3/5-32 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Mervill, Fred H, October 1972 - December 1977; AD12.10.3/5-33 (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Morell, George (Black Mountain Ranch), September 1972 - July 1978; AD12.10.3/5-34 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Morell, George (Black Mountain Ranch), December 1979; AD12.10.3/5-34.5 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Pacific Gas and Electric Fund, August 1976 - July 1979; AD12.10.3/5-35 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Nissan Motor Corp, August 1976 - September 1978; AD12.10.3/5-36 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Nichols, Jesse, Mr. and Mrs, January 1972 - February 1976; AD12.10.3/5-37 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Packard, David, Mr. and Mrs, March 1976 - March 1979; AD12.10.3/5-38 (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - Russell, Mrs. Madeline Haas, August 1966 - January 1979; AD12.10.3/5-41 (Box 34, Folder 40)
  - Scaife Family, July 1967 - May 1979; AD12.10.3/5-42 (Box 34, Folder 41)
  - Sterling, Dr. and Mrs. J.E. Wallace, December 1972 - January 1979; AD12.10.3/5-43 (Box 34, Folder 42)
  - Stewart, Arthur C, May 1973 - November 1978; AD12.10.3/5-44 (Box 34, Folder 43)
  - Sunset Magazine-Lane Publishing Company, December 1971 - May 1979; AD12.10.3/5-45 (Box 34, Folder 44)
  - Syntex Corporation, September 1972 - September 1979; AD12.10.3/5-46 (Box 34, Folder 45)
  - Terman, Dr. and Mrs. Frederick E, December 1972 - November 1978; AD12.10.3/5-47 (Box 34, Folder 46)
  - Varian Corporation and Foundation, January 1966 - September 1978; AD12.10.3/5-48 (Box 34, Folder 47)
  - Xerox Corporation, January 1976 - March 1979; AD12.10.3/5-49 (Box 34, Folder 48)
  - Zellerbach Family Fund, November 1968 - January 1973; AD12.10.3/5-50 (Box 34, Folder 49)
  - Cecil and Ida Green Gifts, October 1976 - June 1979; AD12.10.3/5-52 (Box 34, Folder 50)
  - Charles M. Piggott Gift, June 1973 - June 1979; AD12.10.3/5-53 (Box 34, Folder 51)
  - Miller, Harold A, May 1973 - May 1979; AD12.10.3/5-54 (Box 34, Folder 52)
  - Parents Program/National Chairman, October 1975 - November 1978; AD12.10.3/8 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - University Seminars, September 1978 - September 1979; AD12.10.3/13 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Foundations, Funds, Misc, June 1978 - December 1979; AD12.10.4 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund, October 1979 - July 1979; AD12.10.4/1 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Aaron-Roland Fund for Jewish Students, May 1971 - July 1977; AD12.10.4/2 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Texas Instruments Foundation, July 1978 - May 1979; AD12.10.4/3 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Alcoa Foundation, September 1970 - March 1979; AD12.10.4/4 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Facilitation Fund, October 1975; AD12.10.4/5 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Anonymous Funds, Misc, June 1973 - January 1979; AD12.10.4/7 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Ernest C. Arbuckle Fund, September 1973 - December 1977; AD12.10.4/9 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - ARCS Foundation, December 1973 - February 1979; AD12.10.4/10 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Atlantic Richfield Foundation, October 1972 - August 1979; AD12.10.4/12 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Avalon Foundation, September 1972; AD12.10.4/13 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Babcock Foundation, April 1975 - May 1975; AD12.10.4/14 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Bank of America Foundation, June 1969 - May 1979; AD12.10.4/16 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Baxter Foundation, January 1973 - January 1975; AD12.10.4/17 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Lowell W. Berry Fund, January 1976 - April 1979; AD12.10.4/18 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - The Charles R. Blyth Fund, December 1978 - June 1979; AD12.10.4/19 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - James G. Boswell Foundation, March 1972 - April 1979; AD12.10.4/21 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Briggs Trust Funds, February 1975 - June 1979; AD12.10.4/23 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Carl F. Braun Trust, October 1970 - March 1979; AD12.10.4/25 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Luke B. Hancock Foundation, June 1972 - May 1978; AD12.10.4/28 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - C. B. S. Foundation, 3/75-10/77; AD12.10.4/30 (Box 35, Folder 22.1)
  - Louis Calder Foundation, June 1972 - July 1978; AD12.10.4/31 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - "The Campaign", 1976 - 1977; AD12.10.4/33 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - "The Campaign", 1976 - 1977; AD12.10.4/33.5 (Box 35, Folder 24.1)
  - Foundation and Corporation Input to the Campaign, June 1974 - February 1978; AD12.10.4/33-2 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - "The Campaign": Executive Committee, 12/75-1/77; AD12.10.4/33-5 (Box 35, Folder 25.1)
  - Faculty Volunteer Group - The Campaign, November 1973 - March 1976; AD12.10.4/33-6 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Major Gift Committee, January 1976 - April 1979; AD12.10.4/33-7 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Post-Campaign Planning, August 1976 - August 1978; AD12.10.4/33-8 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Canfield Foundation, August 1972 - October 1975; AD12.10.4/34 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Cap and Gown Fund, July 1972 - July 1979; AD12.10.4/35 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Carnation Foundation, May 1972 - June 1979; AD12.10.4/36 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Carnegie Institution of Washington, February 1974 - December 1976; AD12.10.4/37 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Coro Foundation, April 1972 - July 1979; AD12.10.4/38 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Mobil Corp/Foundation, May 1974 - May 1979; AD12.10.4/39 (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - Edna Clark Foundation, December 1970 - December 1976; AD12.10.4/41 (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - Commonwealth Foundation, February 1975 - July 1979; AD12.10.4/47 (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - Commonwealth Matching Funds -- Medical Center, April 1972 - November 1973; AD12.10.4/48 (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - S.H. Cowell Foundation, May 1972 - June 1978; AD12.10.4/50 (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - Council on Foundations, Incorporated, June 1977 - May 1979; AD12.10.4/51 (Box 35, Folder 39)
  - Elizabeth Rankin Crossett Fund, January 1973 - August 1978; AD12.10.4/52 (Box 35, Folder 40)
  - Crown Zellerbach Foundation, September 1970 - March 1976; AD12.10.4/53 (Box 35, Folder 41)
  - Danforth Foundation, February 1976 - September 1979; AD12.10.4/55 (Box 35, Folder 42)
  - Arthur Vining Davis Foundation, June 1970 - February 1978; AD12.10.4/56 (Box 35, Folder 43)
  - Wm. H. Donner Foundation, December 1972; AD12.10.4/59 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - C and H Dreyfus Foundation, May 1982 - January 1979; AD12.10.4/60 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Earhart Foundation, February 1976 - November 1979; AD12.10.4/61 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Educational Foundation, July 1973 - June 1979; AD12.10.4/62 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Exxon Educational Foundation (formerly ESSO), December 1975 - August 1979; AD12.10.4/67 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Fleishmann Foundation, July 1977 - August 1979; AD12.10.4/69 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Fluor Foundation, December 1970 - July 1979; AD12.10.4/70 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Ford Foundation, September 1977 - August 1979; AD12.10.4/71 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Ford Foundation, September 1977 - August 1979; AD12.10.4/71 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - General Electric Foundation, December 1972 - June 1979; AD12.10.4/78 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Grant Foundation, February 1972 - October 1978; AD12.10.4/81 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Hammer and Coffin Fund, November 1970 - March 1976; AD12.10.4/84 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - John A. Hartford Foundation, November 1970 - March 1976; AD12.10.4/85 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Hazen Foundation, October 1970 - January 1979; AD12.10.4/86 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Wm. Randolph Hearst Foundation, May 1972 - July 1979; AD12.10.4/87 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Albert J. Hettinger, Jr. Fund, January 1973 - August 1978; AD12.10.4/89 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Nathan Hofheimer Foundation, June 1972 - December 1974; AD12.10.4/91 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Hoffman-Laroche Foundation, April 1970 - November 1973; AD12.10.4/92 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Hoover Foundation, December 1971 - January 1978; AD12.10.4/95 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Hope Foundation, February 1970 - July 1970; AD12.10.4/99 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - James Irvine Foundation, January 1976 - May 1979; AD12.10.4/103 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - J. Hugh Jackson Foundation, June 1972 - February 1974; AD12.10.4/105 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Johnson Foundation, December 1970 - May 1979; AD12.10.4/107 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Max Kade Foundation, September 1972 - September 1976; AD12.10.4/109 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Henry J. Kaiser Fund, March 1972 - June 1979; AD12.10.4/110 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Martin Luther King Memorial Fund, February 1971 - January 1976; AD12.10.4/116 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Kresge Foundation, January 1976 - August 1979; AD12.10.4/117 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Kress Foundation, August 1971 - September 1976; AD12.10.4/118 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Lakeside Foundation, June 1971 - May 1979; AD12.10.4/119 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - E.H. and Helen Land Fund, Inc, September 1970 - May 1977; AD12.10.4/121 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Linkletter Foundation, January 1970 - April 1977; AD12.10.4/125 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Henry Luce Foundation, September 1976 - April 1979; AD12.10.4/126 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Anita Oliver Lunn Foundation, July 1971 - January 1979; AD12.10.4/127 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Louis Lurie Foundation, July 1970 - June 1979; AD12.10.4/128 (Box 36, Folder 34)